Asad Siddiqui

Software Developer

५ (905) 749-3964 | **■** asad.h.siddiqui@hotmail.com

Professional Summary

Full Stack developer with 3+ years of experience in ReactJs and NodeJs, with a Bachelor of Computing from University of Guelph. As well as over 2+ years experience in a leadership role, leading teams in multiple Agile software development projects. Looking to leverage my knowledge and skills in a new environment.

Skills

- ReactJs & NodeJs
- UI/UX

- Angular & Flask
- MySQL & PostgreSQL
- Database Administration
- Project Management

Professional Experience

Zebra Robotics, Mississauga, ON - IT Systems Manager

IT Application Lead

April 2024 - Present Nov 2021 - April 2024

- Project Management
 - Met with company Co-Founders to understand, prioritize, and define project tasks and objectives for multiple projects
- Training and Mentoring
 - Training new team members with Full Stack development and Zebra Robotics's environment
- Development
 - Developing full stack features in multiple different projects
 - 4 Reactis projects
 - 2 NodeJs RESTful APIs
 - 4 databases

Projects

Zebra Robotics.com

zebrarobotics.com

Nov 2021 - Present

Helped design and create Zebra Robotics' customer facing website. This website handles credit/debit transactions, features a cart, and features multiple forms where customers can reach out to different locations.

Zebra Robotics Portal

portal.zebrarobotics.com

Nov 2021 - Present

Helped design the Portal to complete the Zebra Robotics environment. The portal system connects to the Zebra Robotics websites and picks up transactions and allows staff members to track payments, schedule classes and manage family profiles for their customers.

STRIPE Competition Website

stripecompetition.com

Mar 2023 - Present

Zebra Robotics Auto-Grader

Sept 2022 - Present

Education

University Of Guelph - B. Comp.

September 2015 - December 2019